[
    { "question" : "있다", "answer" : "to exist", "pronunciation" : "itda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "하다", "answer" : "to do", "pronunciation" : "hada", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "있다", "answer" : "to have", "pronunciation" : "itda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "가다", "answer" : "to go", "pronunciation" : "gada", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "오다", "answer" : "to come", "pronunciation" : "oda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "말하다", "answer" : "to speak", "pronunciation" : "malhada", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "되다", "answer" : "to become", "pronunciation" : "doeda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "보다", "answer" : "to see", "pronunciation" : "boda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "듣다", "answer" : "to listen", "pronunciation" : "deutda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "먹다", "answer" : "to eat", "pronunciation" : "meokda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "자다", "answer" : "to sleep", "pronunciation" : "jada", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "살다", "answer" : "to live", "pronunciation" : "salda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "쓰다", "answer" : "to write", "pronunciation" : "sseuda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "공부하다", "answer" : "to study", "pronunciation" : "gongbuhada", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "생각하다", "answer" : "to think", "pronunciation" : "saenggakhada", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "알다", "answer" : "to know", "pronunciation" : "alda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "사랑하다", "answer" : "to love", "pronunciation" : "saranghada", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "일하다", "answer" : "to work", "pronunciation" : "ilhada", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "걷다", "answer" : "to walk", "pronunciation" : "geotda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "좋아하다", "answer" : "to like", "pronunciation" : "joahada", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "보내다", "answer" : "to send", "pronunciation" : "bonaeda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "놀다", "answer" : "to play", "pronunciation" : "nolda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "이야기하다", "answer" : "to talk", "pronunciation" : "iyagihada", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "기다리다", "answer" : "to wait", "pronunciation" : "gidarida", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "도와주다", "answer" : "to help", "pronunciation" : "dowajuda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "만나다", "answer" : "to meet", "pronunciation" : "mannada", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "찾다", "answer" : "to find", "pronunciation" : "chatda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "출발하다", "answer" : "to depart", "pronunciation" : "chulbalhada", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "돌아오다", "answer" : "to return", "pronunciation" : "dolaoda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "식사하다", "answer" : "to have a meal", "pronunciation" : "siksahada", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "타다", "answer" : "to ride", "pronunciation" : "tada", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "이해하다", "answer" : "to understand", "pronunciation" : "ihaehada", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "좋다", "answer" : "to be good", "pronunciation" : "joda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "맛보다", "answer" : "to taste", "pronunciation" : "matboda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "이루다", "answer" : "to achieve", "pronunciation" : "iruda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "보호하다", "answer" : "to protect", "pronunciation" : "bohohada", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "춤추다", "answer" : "to dance", "pronunciation" : "chumchuda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "마시다", "answer" : "to drink", "pronunciation" : "masida", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "떠나다", "answer" : "to leave", "pronunciation" : "tteonada", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "공연하다", "answer" : "to perform", "pronunciation" : "gongyeonhada", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "열다", "answer" : "to open", "pronunciation" : "yeolda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "닫다", "answer" : "to close", "pronunciation" : "datda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "부르다", "answer" : "to call", "pronunciation" : "bureuda", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "가족", "answer" : "family", "pronunciation" : "gajok", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "친구", "answer" : "friend", "pronunciation" : "chingu", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "학교", "answer" : "school", "pronunciation" : "hakgyo", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "시간", "answer" : "time", "pronunciation" : "sigan", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "사람", "answer" : "person", "pronunciation" : "saram", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "음식", "answer" : "food", "pronunciation" : "eumsik", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "집", "answer" : "house", "pronunciation" : "jip", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "돈", "answer" : "money", "pronunciation" : "don", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "일", "answer" : "work", "pronunciation" : "il", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "여행", "answer" : "travel", "pronunciation" : "yeohaeng", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "병원", "answer" : "hospital", "pronunciation" : "byeongwon", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "옷", "answer" : "clothes", "pronunciation" : "ot", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "책", "answer" : "book", "pronunciation" : "chaek", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "노래", "answer" : "song", "pronunciation" : "nolae", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "컴퓨터", "answer" : "computer", "pronunciation" : "keompyuteo", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "차", "answer" : "car", "pronunciation" : "cha", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "사랑", "answer" : "love", "pronunciation" : "sarang", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "언어", "answer" : "language", "pronunciation" : "eoneo", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "연습", "answer" : "practice", "pronunciation" : "yeonseup", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "시장", "answer" : "market", "pronunciation" : "sijang", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "국제공항", "answer" : "airport", "pronunciation" : "gukjegonghang", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "역", "answer" : "station", "pronunciation" : "yeok", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "버스", "answer" : "bus", "pronunciation" : "beoseu", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "자동차", "answer" : "automobile", "pronunciation" : "jadongcha", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "지하철", "answer" : "subway", "pronunciation" : "jihacheol", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "가방", "answer" : "bag", "pronunciation" : "gabang", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "신발", "answer" : "shoes", "pronunciation" : "sinbal", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "지갑", "answer" : "wallet", "pronunciation" : "jigap", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "날씨", "answer" : "weather", "pronunciation" : "nalssi", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "공원", "answer" : "park", "pronunciation" : "gongwon", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "해변", "answer" : "beach", "pronunciation" : "haebyeon", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "강", "answer" : "river", "pronunciation" : "gang", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "산", "answer" : "mountain", "pronunciation" : "san", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "해외여행", "answer" : "overseas travel", "pronunciation" : "haeoiyeohaeng", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "공항", "answer" : "airport", "pronunciation" : "gonghang", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "마을", "answer" : "village", "pronunciation" : "maeul", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "도시", "answer" : "city", "pronunciation" : "dosi", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "수영", "answer" : "swimming", "pronunciation" : "suyeong", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "스포츠", "answer" : "sports", "pronunciation" : "seupocheu", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "운동", "answer" : "exercise", "pronunciation" : "undong", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "문화", "answer" : "culture", "pronunciation" : "munhwa", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "여행사", "answer" : "travel agency", "pronunciation" : "yeohaengsa", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "관광", "answer" : "sightseeing", "pronunciation" : "gwangwang", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "역사", "answer" : "history", "pronunciation" : "yeoksa", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "예술", "answer" : "art", "pronunciation" : "yesul", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "공연", "answer" : "performance", "pronunciation" : "gongyeon", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "박물관", "answer" : "museum", "pronunciation" : "bakmulgwan", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "전시회", "answer" : "exhibition", "pronunciation" : "jeonsihoe", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "휴가", "answer" : "vacation", "pronunciation" : "hyuga", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "일정", "answer" : "schedule", "pronunciation" : "iljeong", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "좋다", "answer" : "good", "pronunciation" : "jota", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "크다", "answer" : "big", "pronunciation" : "keuda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "작다", "answer" : "small", "pronunciation" : "jakda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "많다", "answer" : "many", "pronunciation" : "manhda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "적다", "answer" : "few", "pronunciation" : "jeokda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "높다", "answer" : "high", "pronunciation" : "nopda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "낮다", "answer" : "low", "pronunciation" : "natda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "가깝다", "answer" : "near", "pronunciation" : "gakkapda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "멀다", "answer" : "far", "pronunciation" : "meolda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "빠르다", "answer" : "fast", "pronunciation" : "ppareuda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "느리다", "answer" : "slow", "pronunciation" : "neurida", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "어떤", "answer" : "what kind of", "pronunciation" : "eotteon", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "간단하다", "answer" : "simple", "pronunciation" : "gandanada", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "복잡하다", "answer" : "complicated", "pronunciation" : "bogjaphada", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "쉽다", "answer" : "easy", "pronunciation" : "swipda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "어렵다", "answer" : "difficult", "pronunciation" : "eoryeopda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "예쁘다", "answer" : "pretty", "pronunciation" : "yeppeuda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "멋지다", "answer" : "cool", "pronunciation" : "meotjida", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "귀엽다", "answer" : "cute", "pronunciation" : "gwiyeopda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "이상하다", "answer" : "strange", "pronunciation" : "isanghada", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "착하다", "answer" : "kind", "pronunciation" : "chakhada", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "나쁘다", "answer" : "bad", "pronunciation" : "nappeuda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "좁다", "answer" : "narrow", "pronunciation" : "jopda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "넓다", "answer" : "wide", "pronunciation" : "neolbda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "더럽다", "answer" : "dirty", "pronunciation" : "deoreopda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "깨끗하다", "answer" : "clean", "pronunciation" : "kkaekkeuthada", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "맛있다", "answer" : "delicious", "pronunciation" : "masitda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "신선하다", "answer" : "fresh", "pronunciation" : "sinseonhada", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "시끄럽다", "answer" : "noisy", "pronunciation" : "sikkeureopda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "조용하다", "answer" : "quiet", "pronunciation" : "joyonghada", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "부드럽다", "answer" : "soft", "pronunciation" : "budeureopda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "따뜻하다", "answer" : "warm", "pronunciation" : "ttatteuthada", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "차갑다", "answer" : "cold", "pronunciation" : "chagapda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "무겁다", "answer" : "heavy", "pronunciation" : "mugeopda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "가볍다", "answer" : "light", "pronunciation" : "gabyeopda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "얇다", "answer" : "thin", "pronunciation" : "yapda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "두껍다", "answer" : "thick", "pronunciation" : "dukkeopda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "새롭다", "answer" : "new", "pronunciation" : "saeropda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "오래되다", "answer" : "old", "pronunciation" : "oraedwida", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "늙다", "answer" : "old", "pronunciation" : "neukda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "건강하다", "answer" : "healthy", "pronunciation" : "geonganghada", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "아프다", "answer" : "sick", "pronunciation" : "apeuda", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "잘", "answer" : "well", "pronunciation" : "jal", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "빨리", "answer" : "quickly", "pronunciation" : "ppalli", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "많이", "answer" : "much", "pronunciation" : "mani", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "자주", "answer" : "often", "pronunciation" : "jaju", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "정말", "answer" : "really", "pronunciation" : "jeongmal", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "늘", "answer" : "always", "pronunciation" : "neul", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "다시", "answer" : "again", "pronunciation" : "dasi", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "저절로", "answer" : "automatically", "pronunciation" : "jeojeollo", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "아마", "answer" : "maybe", "pronunciation" : "ama", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "조금", "answer" : "a little", "pronunciation" : "jogeum", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "여전히", "answer" : "still", "pronunciation" : "yeojeonhi", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "이제", "answer" : "now", "pronunciation" : "ije", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "어디서나", "answer" : "everywhere", "pronunciation" : "eodiseona", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "한번", "answer" : "once", "pronunciation" : "hanbeon", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "대개", "answer" : "mostly", "pronunciation" : "daegae", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "차마", "answer" : "cannot possibly", "pronunciation" : "chama", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "아직", "answer" : "yet", "pronunciation" : "ajik", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "그렇게", "answer" : "thus", "pronunciation" : "geureohge", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "언제나", "answer" : "always", "pronunciation" : "eonjena", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "고마", "answer" : "thankfully", "pronunciation" : "goma", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" }
]